[
    {
      "question": "How can we generate random numbers in python using methods?",
      "choice1": "random.uniform ()",
      "choice2": "random.randint()",
      "choice3": "random.random()",
      "choice4": "All of the above",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What command is used to shuffle a list ‘L’ ",
      "choice1": "L.shuffle()",
      "choice2": "random.shufflelist(L)",
      "choice3": "shuffle(L)",
      "choice4": "random.Shuffle(L)",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which code is used to open a file for binary writing?",
      "choice1": "'w'",
      "choice2": "'wb'",
      "choice3": "'r+'",
      "choice4": "'a'",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which module is used in python to create Graphics?",
      "choice1": "Turtle",
      "choice2": "Canvas",
      "choice3": "Tkinter",
      "choice4": "Graphics",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Given a function that does not return any value, what value is shown when executed at the shell?",
      "choice1": "int",
      "choice2": "bool",
      "choice3": "void",
      "choice4": "None",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a complex number?",
      "choice1": "k = 2 + 3j",
      "choice2": "k = complex(2, 3)",
      "choice3": "k = 2 + 3l",
      "choice4": "k = 2 + 3J",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What does ~~~~~~5 evaluate to?",
      "choice1": "+5",
      "choice2": "-11",
      "choice3": "+11",
      "choice4": "-5",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Given a string s = “Welcome”, which of the following code is incorrect?",
      "choice1": "print s[0]",
      "choice2": "print s.lower()",
      "choice3": "s[1] = ‘r’",
      "choice4": "print s.strip()",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "________ is a simple but incomplete version of a function.",
      "choice1": "Stub",
      "choice2": "Function",
      "choice3": "A function developed using bottom - up approach",
      "choice4": "A function developed using top - down approach",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "To start Python from the command prompt, use the command: ",
      "choice1": "execute python",
      "choice2": "go python",
      "choice3": "python",
      "choice4": "run python",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct about Python?",
      "choice1": "It supports automatic garbage collection",
      "choice2": "It can be easily integrated with C, C++, COM, ActiveX, CORBA, and Java",
      "choice3": "Both of the above",
      "choice4": "None of the above",
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
  